{
	"response_code": 0,
	"results": [{
		"category": "Test",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"question": "This is question one?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["Wu-Tang Clan", "Run-D.M.C.", "Beastie Boys"]
	}, {
		"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"question": "This is question two?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["Nintendo", "EA", "Sony"]
	}, {
		"category": "This is question three?",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"question": "What is the standard frame rate for animation?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["12 FPS", "30 FPS", "60 FPS"]
	}, {
		"category": "This is question four?",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"question": "Which souls game was not directed by Hidetaka Miyazaki?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["Demon Souls", "Dark Souls", "Dark Souls 3"]
	}, {
		"category": "Vehicles",
		"type": "boolean",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"question": "This is question five?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["True"]
	}, {
		"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"question": "This is question six?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["2007", "2004", "2005"]
	}, {
		"category": "History",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"question": "This is question seven?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["100", "90", "101"]
	}, {
		"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"question": "This is question eight?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Kyoto Animation"]
	}, {
		"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"question": "This is question nine?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["Diarmid", "Hareth", "Gerent"]
	}, {
		"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
		"type": "multiple",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"question": "This is question ten?",
		"correct_answer": "This is Correct",
		"incorrect_answers": ["Battlefield Vietnam", "Battlefield 2", "Battlefield 1"]
	}]
}
